University Photograph; Collection ua390
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Aerial photographof the University at Albany's uptown campus., ca. 1980
- Aerial photograph of the University at Albany's downtown campus, ca. 1980
- A picture of an unidentified State University of New York at Albany football player attempting to catch the football with a large number of opponents nearby., 1980
- A picture of Dave Machson, a State University of New York at Albany football player, tackling an opponent. In the bottom margin is written "Dave Machson" and "61% 1-L.", 1980
- A picture of student Afrim Nezaj, a soccer player for the State University of New York at Albany soccer team, in the middle of a play during a soccer match. In the top margin, a check mark, the numeral 2, an "x" or a lowercase letter x, a crossed out "103%," and several indeterminable marks., 1980
- University at Albany students dancing with Latin dancers under the vaulted halls outside the Campus Center., 1980
- A picture of State University of New York at Albany football players -- and their opponents -- in the middle of a play during a football game., 1980
- A picture of visitors from Brazil in one of the Uptown Campus buildings, January 1980. "Uptown Campus" became an official designation for the State University of New York at Albany's campus at 1400 Washington Avenue, Albany, N.Y. in the fall of 1975.
- Two unidentified students talking on the Academic Podium at the State University of New York uptown campus., 1980
- Albert C. Mossin, State University of New York at Albany faculty member in the School of Business, lecturing to a group assembled in a classroom. Duplicate of 3005., 1980
- Three unidentified students attending a class at the State University of New York at Albany., 1980
- State University of New York at Albany's Gary Grold teaching a class, with mostly adult students, circa 1980.
- A faculty member lecturing to students in what appears to be a Classics or an Art History class. There are crop marks and instructions to "reduce to 29 picas" in the top margin (bewtween arrows) and to "reduce to 19 picas" (between arrows) in the left margin., 1980
- Nell Sedransk, a State University of New York at Albany Mathematics faculty member (on the viewer's left), working with a student., 1980
- A close-up picture of student Afrim Nezaj, a soccer player for the State University of New York at Albany soccer team. There are crop marks on all sides of the photograph. In the right margin is written "reduce to 12 picas" (between arrows); in the bottom margin is written "reduce to 9 picas" (between arrows); and in the left margin is written "PHOTO D.", 1980
- A close-up of Charles S. Dawson, a member of the State University of New York at Albany Men's Physical Education staff and coaching staff. In this picture he is wearing a shirt for the soccer program. There are crop marks on all sides of the photograph. In the right margin is written "reduce to 12 picas" (between arrows); in the bottom margin is written "reduce to 9 picas" (between arrows); and in the left margin is written "PHOTO A.", 1980
- A close-up picture of someone named Sterfin who is wearing a soccer jersey. There are crop marks on all sides of the photograph. In the right margin is written "reduce to 12 picas" (between arrows); in the bottom margin is written "reduce to 9 picas" (between arrows); and in the left margin is written "PHOTO F" with a crossed out character., 1980
- Vincent O'Leary, Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990, with other people in a group portrait. O'Leary is the gentleman with glasses, third from the viewer's right. During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing. There are crop marks on three of four corners and along the bottom border are instructions written, "REDUCE TO 448 77%" and 11-A.", 1980
- Vincent O'Leary, Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990, at a reception. During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing. There are crop marks and some instruction written regarding editing the photograph size. Also written is "PHOTO 4" at the top center of the picture., 1980
- Two female students in class, one of whom is speaking. There are crop marks on all four sides and words written in the margins, which read: "REDUCE TO 29‪‪‪⁯'s" (within arrows) and "H" in the bottom margin; and "to 24⁯'s" (within arrows) in the left margin., 1980
- A photograph of the entrance to the general dining area in the Campus Center at the State University of New York at Albany. The photograph was taken with a fisheye lens, a wide-angle lens which creates a distorted image., 1980
- Two unidentified students talking on the Acaemic Podium at the State University of New York at Albany uptown campus. There are crop marks in the left and bottom margins. Written in the left margin is "Reduce to 24 pi" and in the bottom margin is "Reduce to 29 pi" and "Photo F, p6 77% of original.", 1980
- A picture of students playing a leisurely game of baseball on the lawn within the traffic circle, State University of New York at Albany Uptown Campus. The traffic circle was renamed Collins Circle on June 8, 1991 in honor of Evan R. Collins, former President of the institution. There are crop marks on two sides of the photograph and in the bottom margin is written "77% Pix M 7 3/8"W. x 4 3/4" D." The letter "M" is enclosed in a circle., 1980
- Two unidentified students sitting on the Academic Podium at the State University of New York at Albany., 1980
- Lester B. Brown, Professor of Social Welfare, discussing a paper with a student. There are crop marks and instuctions to "reduce to 24 picas" (between arrows) in the top margin and "reduce to 14 picas" (between arrows) in the right margin. In the bottom margin is noted, "PHOTO H.", 1980
- The 1980 Telethon staffers Linda Hischoffer, Mike Hellerman (State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1981), Joy Prefer (State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1980), Stuart Gruskin (State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1980), and Marlene Michaelson (State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1980) with children from the Wildwood Program at the Telethon's Halloween party. There are crop marks on all sides of the photograph. In the top margin is written "REDUCE TO 44_'s" (inside arrows); in the left margin is written, "REDUCE TO 35 1/2 _'s" (inside arrows); and in the right margin is written "136.8 LL."
- Two unidentified students of the State University of New York at Albany participating in tutoring session., 1980
- Sam Wakshull, United University Professions (UUP) president from 1975 to 1981, taking a stack of Save SUNY petitons from an Susan Ward, president of Student Association of SUNY (SASU), during a Save SUNY press conference., 1980
- An unidentified State University of New york at Albany faculty member lecturing to students in the Lecture Center. It appears to be a class in the Department of Music due to the presence of the pianos, musical notation blackboard, and audio equipment., 1980
- Unidentified students on the Academic Podium at the State University of New York at Albany. One student is petting a dog., 1980
- An unidentified State University of New York at Albany female student napping on campus., 1980
- A faculty meeting at the State University of New York at Albany in progress., 1980
- Two unidentified students grasping hands in greeting, possibly upon moving into a dormitory. One is holding a rolled carpet on his shoulder, and there is a television in the background., 1980
- A picture of students who are repainting playground equipment as part of a urban beautification project. The students also are instructing children as they help in the project. There are crop marks on all sides of the photograph. In the right margin is written "REDUCE TO 25 1/2_'S" (between arrows); in the bottom margin is written "REDUCE TO 29_'S," an uppercase letter "J," and "68.5" (between arrows)., 1980
- Nell Sedransk, a State University of New York at Albany Mathematics faculty member, instructing a student., 1980
- Students congregated near the smaller fountain outside the Campus Center on the Uptown Campus. There is almost a mirror-like reflection of the students in the still fountain water., 1980
- An unidentified State University of New York at Albany faculty member lecturing to students in the Lecture Center. It appears to be a class in the Department of Music due to the presence of the pianos, musical notation blackboard, and audio equipment., 1980
- An unidentified student walking on the State University of New York at Albany campus., 1980
- An unidentified female student listening to a lecture at the State University of New York at Albany. There are crop marks in all margins of the original. Written in the left margin between two arrows is "enlarge to 38 picas" and in the bottom margin is "p.24" and between two arrows is "enlarge to 44 picas.", 1980
- A faculty member lecturing to students in what appears to be a Classics or an Art History class. There are crop marks and instructions to "reduce to 18.5 picas" in the top margin and to "reduce to 16 picas" (between arrows) in the left margin., 1980
- A close-up picture of John M. Markes (?), State University of New York at Albany soccer player and member of the Class of 1983. There are crop marks on all sides of the photograph. In the right margin is written "reduce to 12 picas" (between arrows); in the bottom margin is written "reduce to 9 picas" (between arrows); and in the left margin is written "PHOTO C.", 1980
- An unidentified student reading a market management book in a class at the State University of New York at Albany. There are crop marks in all margins of the original., 1980
- A close-up picture of an unidentified member of the coaching staff. In this picture he is wearing a shirt for the soccer program. There are crop marks on all sides of the photograph. In the right margin is written "reduce to 12 picas" (between arrows); in the bottom margin is written "reduce to 9 picas" (between arrows); and in the left margin is written "PHOTO B." The name Malubarry and Walntarry have been assigned to this individual., 1980
- A group of students, browsing through record albums being sold on the Academic Podium of the uptown campus. There are crop marks and instruction to "reduce to 29 picas" (between arrows) in the top margin and to "reduce to 24 picas" (between arrows) in the left margin. In the bottom margin is noted "57%" and two triangles are drawn in the lower right corner., 1980
- An unidentified student attending a class at the State University of New York at Albany. There are crop marks in the top and left margins. Written in the left margin is "Photo M 77% of original P.19." Written in the top margin between two arrows is "reduce to 29 pi" and between to arrows in the left margin is "reduce to 24 pi.", 1980
- Two unidentified students looking at something, possibly an event posting, at the State University of New York at Albany., 1980
- An unidentified female student studying in the University Library at the State University of New York at Albany. There are crop marks in ht top and right margins. Written in the bottom margin is "9846.62.C." Written in the reverse is "Will.", 1980
- Judi B. Jacobs, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1983, talking on the telephone., 1980
- An unidentified female student at the State University of New York at Albany making a measurement on a flat surface. There are crop marks on all sides of the original. Written in the right margin is "NOTE: CROPS ON SLANT." Written in the right margin between two arrows is "21 3/4%" "REDUCE TO 12 (square)s" and "B." Written in the bottom margin between two arrows is "REDUCE TO 7 1/2 (square)s.", 1980
- An unidentified man singing into a microphone and playing the guitar on the Academic Podium at the State University of New York at Albany., 1980
- An unidentified man working in a radio station associated with the State University of New York at Albany. There are crop marks on all sides of the original. Written in the right margin is "APRIL (RIGH)." Written in the top margin between two arrows is "to 29.5 PICAS" and in the left margin between two arrows is "to 48 PICAS." Written on the reverse is "AMRON.", 1980
- A picture of a male student showing affection to his dog. The scene is either just before or after a game of baseball on the lawn, which borders the traffic circle of the uptown campus. Featured prominently in the picture is Dutch Quadrangle's Stuyvesant Residence Tower and what was the Administration Building (now the Arts and Sciences Building). There are crop marks and in the top and left margins there are written directions to "reduce to 14 picas" (between arrows) and in the left margin there also is a barely legible direction referencing "50%.", 1980
- An unidentified male student practicing skateboard tricks on the Academic Podium of the uptown campus., 1980
- Unidentified students attending a lecture at the State University of New York at Albany. There are crop marks in the right, bottom, and left margins of the original. Written in the top margin is "duotone," and in the bottom margin is written "9846 39-B 55%.", 1980
- Two unidentified State University of New York at Albany students working on the layout of pages, perhaps of a newspaper, to be printed or published., 1980
- Two unidentified State University of New York at Albany students standing by an open filing cabinet looking at a folder., 1980
- Two unidentified students of the State University of New York at Albany participating in tutoring session., 1980
- Lester B. Brown, Professor of Social Welfare, discussing a paper with a student. There are crop marks and instructions to "reduce to 29 picas" (between arrows) in the top margin and "reduce to 19 picas" (between arrows) in the left margin. In the bottom margin is noted, "Photo H p. 9 52% of original.", 1980
- A picture of Nell Sedransk, a Mathematics faculty member, instructing a student., 1980
- An unidentified student sitting on the Academic Podium at the State University of New York at Albany., 1980
- An unidentfied female student walking away from one of the quadrangles at the State University of New York at Albany uptown campus. There are crop marksi all margins of the original. Written in the top margin is "(2)" and "B", in the right margin is "1.05" and in the left margin is "Photo B." Written in the bottom margin between two arrows is "reduce to 15.5 picas.", 1980
- An unidentified male student taking notes in class at the State University of New York at Albany. There are corp marks in all margins of the original. Written in the left margin is "p.19." Written between two arrows in the bottom margin is "reduce to 19 picas" and in the right margin between two arrows is "to 34.", 1980
- An unidentified male student lounging outside and drinking a beverage at the State University of New York at Albany uptown campus., 1980
- An unidentified student at the State University of New York at Albany, possibly Deb Lawrence., 1980
- A picture of State University of New York at Albany football players throwing the ball., 1980
- A picture of State University of New York at Albany football players sitting on a bench, during a game. In the bottom margin is written "Dave Machson.", 1980
- A close-up picture of Richard Pagano (?), a soccer player for the State University of New York at Albany soccer team and member of the Class of 1984. There are crop marks on all sides of the photograph. In the right margin is written "reduce to 12 picas" (between arrows); in the bottom margin is written "reduce to 9 picas" (between arrows); and in the left margin is written "PHOTO E.", 1980
- Unidentified students working on an urban neighborhood clean up project as children observe; most likely in Albany, NY., 1980
- State University of New York at Albany students cleaning the grounds and equipment on a playground as part of a urban beautification project., 1980
- Vincent O'Leary, Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990, on HAP Day (Human Awareness Potential Day). During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing., 1980
- K. (Kirkland) Leroy Irvis, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1938. Irvis was the 130th Speaker of the House of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania -- the first African American speaker in both Pennsylvania and in the United States. He is also renowned as an artist, poet, and scholar., 1980
- Unidentified students of the State University of New york at Albany practicing water-related first aid and rescue techniques., 1980
- A student playing a violin in a performance on the State University of New York at Albany's uptown campus. A dulcimer is in the foreground., 1980
- A picture of an unidentified student conducting a scientific experiment in a lab at the State University of New York at Albany. There are crop marks on all sides of the original., 1980
- Lester B. Brown, Professor of Social Welfare at the State University of New York at Albany, discussing a paper with a student., 1980
- An unidentified student at the State University of New York at Albany., 1980
- A portrait of an unidentified male student at the State University of New York at Albany., 1980
- An unidentified intern at the State University of New York at Albany using a computer., 1980
- A picture of unidentified football players between plays. The game is taking place on the uptown campus of the State University of New York at Albany., 1980
- Two unidentified students sitting and eating on the Adademic Podium at the State University of New York at Albany. There are crop marks on all sides of the original. Written in the bottom margin is "F (FLOPPED)" and "F." Written in the left margin between two arrows is "TO 19 3/4 (square)s" and in the top margin between two arrows is "TO 17 (square)s.", 1980
- Three unidentified students talking on the Academic Podium at the State University of New York at Albany. One student is wearing a shirt with a football on it, with the writing "Newburgh Pop Warner Football.", 1980
- An unidentified man and woman having a conversation while sitting on the Academic Podium of the uptown campus. In the lower right corner is noted, "AA.", 1980
- Actors Kris Kristofferson and Jane Fonda photographed during the making of the film "Rollover." This photo was taken in the Campus Center Assembly Hall. Assembly Hall was converted to look like an Arabic palace because of its interior architecture., 1980
- Two unidentified students relaxing outside at the State University of New York at Albany. Duplicate, but mirror image, of 16980 and 3156., 1980 January 18
- Two unidentified students relaxing outside at the State University of New York at Albany. Duplicate of 3156, mirror image of 13400., 1980 January 18
- Unidentified students listening to a lecture at the State University of New York at Albany. There are crop marks in all margins of the original., 1980 January 21
- Unidentified students listening to a lecture at the State University of New York at Albany. There are crop marks in the top and right margins of the original. Written in the bottom margin is "Pix I" "2 5/16"x 2 5/16"" and "37%.", 1980 January 21
- An unidentified male student of the State University of New York at Albany sitting by a blackboard in a classroom during a lecture at the State University of New York at Albany. There are crop marks in all margins of the original., 1980 January 21
- Unidentified students listening to a lecture in class at the State University of New York at Albany., 1980 January 21
- Unidentified students listening to a lecture at the State University of New York at Albany., 1980 February 21
- A picture of Paul Miesing, State University of New York at Albany faculty member in the School of Business, sitting in his office., 1980 March
- A picture of Lynne Tamor of the State University of New York at Albany's Reading Department. There are crop marks on all sides of the original., 1980 April
- A picture of defensive back Don Bown of the State University of New York at Albany Great Danes with an intercepted pass in a game against Ithaca College, the Division III NCAA football champion, September 13, 1980. The game is taking place on the Uptown Campus., 1980 September 13
- A picture of football players in action as the State University of New York at Albany Great Dane defense attempts to hold the offense of Ithaca College, the Division III NCAA champion, September 13, 1980 -- the game is taking place on the Uptown Campus. There are crop marks on all sides of the photograph. In the top margin is an uppercase letter "K" enclosed in a circle; in the right margin is written "reduce to 29 picas" (between arrows); and in the bottom margin is written "reduce to 44 picas" (between arrows)., 1980 September 13
- Marc F. Duret, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1982. This image appeared in the University News, October 15, 1980, pg.2, with the caption "Marc Duret, an exchange graduate student from France, will play Proteus' servant, Launce, in the University Theatre production of 'The Two Gentlemen of Verona,' Oct. 17-19, in the PAC Main Theatre. Duret has studied at the Conservatoire superieur d'Art Dramatique de Paris and has received acclaim for his acting from France's leading Newspapers." There are crop marks on all sides of the original., 1980 October
- A picture of unidentified participants in a State University of New York at Albany Alumni Association event held in Florida., 1980 November 8
- A picture of unidentified participants in a State University of New York at Albany Alumni Association event held in Florida., 1980 November 8
- A picture of unidentified participants in a State University of New York at Albany Alumni Association event held in Florida., 1980 November 8
- A picture of an unidentified child who is attending a State University of New York at Albany Alumni Association event held in Florida., 1980 November 8
- A picture of unidentified participants in a State University of New York at Albany Alumni Association event held in Florida., 1980 November 8
- A picture of unidentified participants in a State University of New York at Albany Alumni Association event held in Florida., 1980 November 8
- A picture of an unidentified gentleman at a State University of New York at Albany Alumni Association event held in Florida., 1980 November 8
- A picture of an unidentified child who is attending a State University of New York at Albany Alumni Association event held in Florida., 1980 November 8
- A picture of unidentified participants in a State University of New York at Albany Alumni Association event held in Florida., 1980 November 8
- A picture of unidentified participants in a State University of New York at Albany Alumni Association event held in Florida., 1980 November 8
- A picture of an unidentified child who is attending a State University of New York at Albany Alumni Association event held in Florida., 1980 November 8
- A picture of unidentified participants in a State University of New York at Albany Alumni Association event held in Florida., 1980 November 8